Guide to the Stanford University, Plant Services Office, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Stanford University Building Plans (negative prints), Accession ARCH-1991-123
  - Hydraulic Laboratory - Sections (Box 4, Folder 415)
  - Hydraulic Laboratory - Details of Pit Channels and Conduits (Box 4, Folder 416)
  - Hydraulic Laboratory - Details of Roof Truss (Box 4, Folder 417)
  - Hydraulic Laboratory - Details of Roof Truss (Box 4, Folder 418)
  - Plan View of Quadrangle (Box 4, Folder 419)
  - Plan View of Quadrangle (Box 4, Folder 420)
  - Building Plans (negative prints) (Box 5-11)